For Steve, his adventure isn't all black and white.
Penguins is a documentary, family film directed by Alastair Fothergill.
The story of Steve, an Adélie penguin, on a quest to
find a life partner and start a family.
When Steve meets with Wuzzo the emperor penguin they become friends.
But nothing comes easy in the icy Antarctic.
Narrator (voice), played by Ed Helms.
Penguins is a 2019 American nature documentary film
directed by Alastair Fothergill and Jeff Wilson.
The coming-of-age story follows an Adélie penguin named Steve, who joins fellow males in the icy
Antarctic spring on a quest to build a suitable nest, find a life partner and start a family.
The American release of the film is narrated by Ed Helms.
Produced by Disneynature, the film was released in the United States on April 17, 2019, five days before Earth
Day and four years to the day of the release of fellow Disneynature production Monkey Kingdom.
It is the thirteenth nature documentary to be
released under the Disneynature label.
The film received positive reviews from critics, who
singled out the "beautiful cinematography".
The film explores themes of penguin, wildlife,
antarctica, life challenges, mating ritual.